

HAIDAR FAHKRI JAUHAR FIKRI

About Me

"Worked throughout college to cover living and educational expenses, making me an independent, adaptable and always ready to learn new things."



0852-3896-8807



haidarjf07@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/ haidar-fahkrijf-400757248



Jl. Jepara Kudus, No 233 RT 6 RW 1 Margoyoso, Kalinyamatan, Jepara

LANGUAGE

- Indonesia (basic)
- English (Elementary)

EXPERTISE

- MS Office
- Canva
- Visual Studio Code
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Team Working
- Public Speaking

EDUCATION

MUHAMMADIYAH UNIVERSITY OF SEMARANG

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering 2019-2023

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER PT. DUTA SOLUSI INFORMATIKA

12/2022 - 07/2023

- Troubleshot, tested and remedied issues before software deployment.
- Resolved technical problems related to website functionality or performance.
- Developed and maintained websites using HTML, JavaScript, and PHP.

PRIVATE TUTOR EXCELLENT PRIVATE COURSE

08/2020 - 08/2023

- Teaching middle school students all subjects without exception.
- Assisting in completing homework assignments.
- Assisting in guiding students to learn independently, fostering self-reliance, and teaching proper usage of the internet for educational purposes.

ADDMINISTRATION OFFICER BADAN WAKAF AL-QURAN

07/2021 - 11/2022

- Teaching middle school students all subjects without exception.
- Assisting in completing homework assignments.
- Assisting in guiding students to learn independently, fostering self-reliance, and teaching proper usage of the internet for educational purposes.